Good morning
Good morning.
Today is the school festival at our exclusive school!
We've done rehearsal, hair and makeup,
I'm just waiting for the show to start.
It's not quite finished yet.
Is it your lucky day?
Wan wan!
It's so cute!
I like the way you tied it.
Here, I like to tie it at the bottom.
I like to tie it at the bottom.
I like to tie it at the bottom
It goes halfway down
It'll be halfway down
I wanted to cut it a little bit.
Then I'd have to do a bun or something.
It's difficult
Something difficult
It's tokiboro.
I can make it happen.
Tokibaro mask
New hair
This is cute
Lip-chan Hair
Short version of curling morial
Yes, it is.
It's amazing outside too.
Outside the dressing room.
Cute.
What can I say?
the clothes you're wearing
Illustration.
Like a welcome.
He made it for us.
Like a welcome board.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What did you have for breakfast?
I had onigiri for breakfast.
I don't know.
Maybe wakame onigiri.
I used to drink a lot.
Compotage.
You know...
The pumpkin version.
It's delicious, isn't it?
But Hughlytown...
Compotage.
Delicious.
Oh, I haven't had Dale's in a while.
Oh man!
Killamel and And Inn Spice
Spices of Andouine
Spice of Spice
November, then bacon and stuff.
That's why I bought it.
We don't even know what it is.
We'll ask them ourselves.
Stop.
I don't know what it's called.
Not "Sukimeki Movie.
Sukimeki.
It's about a movie that we take by ourselves.
Someone like Sukimeki Movie... Someone like Sukimeki Movie...
There was some kind of name.
Ascending Movie
I hope it goes up. I wonder if there are a lot of students.
I wonder how it's going to go. I'm hungry.
Let's do makeup at a glance today.
No glitter.
Where's Harry Potter of Harry Potter?
I don't know if this is going to make any difference, but Harry Potter's at 31 Harry Potter's is super tasty.
Delicious?
What's good?
Milk tea.
I love milk tea.
I don't really like drinks, but I know what milk tea tastes like, and tea tastes like, and it's delicious.
I don't get that very often, so it's really good.
31 is an iced mile and it's going to be posted in two years.
Gold.
Why is that?
You can use the coupon to get a triple for a double.
Isn't that great?
They'll give you a double card for a tiny popsicle.
Gold.
Dance gold.
So I'll have a triple every time.
That's so weird.
I think it's just a regular normal flavor.
Love Potion 31 or Hoppy Shower or Chocolate.
Normal finumation.
Love Potion 31
Berry Berry Streveler
That one is the best
That one is delicious!
for sure!
It was a Kanik House Reverberner.
I love chocolate!
Congratulations!
Bye-bye.
Ladies and gentlemen, here is your lunch.
Look at this.
Roasted peas!
Yay!
Delicious!
Oh, my God.
What?
Roast beef.
It's so hearty!
I just cut it off.
Oh, that's right.
Congratulations!
Everyone's been working so hard.
Here's your bento!
Yay!
Congratulations!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, Aki-chan
That's great!
I'll give you three.
I'll give you one.
Wow, I'm in.
One.
Oh, my God.
Looks delicious.
It's too good!
Bon appétit!
Too much!
While waiting
So cute!
I just have a lot of free time
So, why are you playing golf so early? One more thing...
Shape
Yes, I'm done.
Thank you for watching.
Is that good?
That's the same as now.
Hiyori, oharu, six, two, oharu, six thousand, six thousand.
Six thousand, two, three, four.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the new Paradise Fischergal!
Good afternoon.
It's going to be a blast.
Endre.
It's Endre.
This is Endre.
ع vet
tue
Oh, actually.
Watch the world. There's nothing to worry about.
Just give me enough to make me laugh
It's a garbage castle
It's a beautiful day, the most powerful star again
The world's most powerful star
Hello to the wonderful world Hello!
Enjoy this video!
And stay tuned for more weather in Camoilles!
Yonne!
ni
etta
dea
iem
Lots and lots and lots
I have to keep on giving.
I'm having the time of my life with my hands.
You're gonna get a hug.
Cute. Cute. Cute.
So cute. So cute. So cute.
Cute, cute, cute. Can't stop loving you.
Hey, my own personal ditching agent, when are you ready?
Cute. Cute.
Cute, cute, too cute
Cute, cute, cute. Kiss, kiss, kiss everything.
Cute. Cute. Cute.
Cute. That's one more.
That's okay.
Paralysis.
I'm just gonna pull you in.
Light.
Right after now.
It's been so long.
I even remember seeing the impatience.
In the back are the two weirdos.
Red
Congratulations!
Yay!
Thank you so much for your voice. I'm so happy already, we were all soaring behind the scenes.
I'm really looking forward to doing it, I really, really want to do it,
But, you know, I'm having a little bit of a hard time learning because of the program, so I'll see you all next time when we do a live concert.
I'm going to do another show next time, and I'm going to have so much fun that I want to be on the stage when everyone shouts "encore",
I would be happy if you could go to the encore again then.
Bye bye, everyone, and please call for an encore.
I look forward to seeing you all again on TV today for another great live show!
Encore and thank you for today!
Now...
Now that's one piece of art.
I'm not backstage at all.
It's over!
The fans were so passionate.
I'm so excited.
I didn't want to let them down.
I tried my best.
But...
What are you holding in your hand?
Right now.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What a surprise.
They're all students.
It's like a song.
That's great.
You guys are amazing.
How did you do it?
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for everything.
I love the anger.
It's been a long time coming.
It's been quite a while since I've heard from you.
It's been a little bit...
I felt like it wasn't going to happen at all.
But the whole time, people were saying things.
I couldn't answer.
I just wanted to say one more time
Thank you.
What's that? Next coach.
Hacky Cree.
I've been saying this to myself since the beginning.
What?
A month?
I don't know, I just don't think I can do Hacky Cree.
I was dancing around it.
That's all I can say.
It's useless.
Not everyone does it.
But...
I'll see you next time.
I'll see you all next time.
Thank you very much.
See you soon.
Goodbye, goodbye. Thank you for yesterday.
After the rain, the streets are turning colors
And on the canvas of our broken hearts, they paint a piece of the future.
And lead us on the way.
by H.
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll go wherever the rain takes me
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me, the streets are shimmering after the rain
My heart is jumping, rainbow pools, rainbow pianos, rainbow pianos, rainbow pianos
My heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my tears are drying, I'm wearing a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
me
Please subscribe to our channel!